### HIEN TRONG TRAN

### FRONT-FND DEVELOPER

➡ https://tranhien-portfolio.vercel.app 👮 https://github.com/hientt1803

I've 8 months of experience in React.js (Next.js) and Java (spring boot). I have worked as a full-stack developer in large and small projects such as managing a programming teaching center, Notion clone, Blog website...

#### **SKILL**

- Proficient: React.js (Next.js), CSS
   (Tailwind, Bootstrap, SCSS,
   Responsive), Java (Core, Spring Boot), SQL (SQL Server, My SQL).
- Familiar: Redux, Typescript, Java Swing, PHP (Laravel), NodeJS, AngularJS.
- Tools: Figma, Firebase, Trello, Junit4, TestNG (basic).
- Other: Restful APIs, working with API, self learning, problem resolve skill.

#### LANGUAGE

English - Top Notch 3

### **EDUCATION**

FPT Polytechnic College Can Tho (August 2021 - December 2023)

- Major: Software Development
- Status: graduated
- Excellent student in year (2023)

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Full-stack developer | Manage programing teaching center | 4-person group project

Development | September 2023 - December 2023

- Tech stack: Java (Spring Boot), RESTful APIs, React.js, Bootstrap, SCSS, SQL Server.
- GitHub: https://github.com/alexnguyen03/f4education
- Project purpose: Created a web application to managing a programming teaching center where they can sold and teach programing with most popular technology.
- Responsibilities:
  - Back-end: Develop backend systems/APIs
  - Fron-end: Create and handle functions shopping cart, checkout, statistics, manager attendance, question banking's, certificate, import export excel file.
- Achieve: How to use React and Java spring boot, MVC, Spring JPA, Restful APIs to build a whole website management a programing teaching center.

## Backend intern at Can Tho University software center (CUSC) for 11 week

Development | September 2023 - November 2023

- Tech stack: PHP (Laravel), MySQL, Swager.
- **GitHub**: <a href="https://github.com/kellyfire611/cusc-his-v3-api">https://github.com/kellyfire611/cusc-his-v3-api</a>
- **Project purpose**: Create a APIs with Laravel 10 and MySQL for website like WordPress where people can drag and drop template available and building there own website.
- Responsibilities: Create whole APIs for website, create a dynamic control for render and download office document(Word, Excel, PowerPoint).
- Achieve: learned how to working with Laravel, MySQL, Docker, MVC and Module structure, working with dynamic render office document (Word, Excel, PDF)

### Full-stack Developer | Notion clone | personal project

Development | January 2024

- **Tech stack**: Next.js, Tailwind, Typescript, Convex, Clerk, Edge Store.
- GitHub: https://github.com/hientt1803/notion-clone
- **Project purpose**: Create a taking note app where people can

note there activity, stories,... and publish them to there friend.

- Responsibilities: Development and deploy website.
- **Achieve:** Learned working with a real-time Database Convex, create custom hooks, build a complex logic UI and functions.
- Website URL: <a href="https://modern-note-taking-app.vercel.app/">https://modern-note-taking-app.vercel.app/</a>

### Full-stack Developer | Blog website | personal project

### Development | January 2024

- Tech stack: Next.js, SCSS, Tailwind, MongoDB, Prisma, Firebase
- **GitHub:** https://github.com/hientt1803/augentern-blog-app
- **Project purpose:** Create an blog website where people can login, write blog, share there stories, like, comment other post.
- Responsibilities: Development and deploy website.
- **Achieve**: Learned how to create a what blog app be with Next.js, Context API and MongoDB to display, create post, like , share,...